junaidjamshed.com 2014-06-29

# Welcome to Junaid Jamshed

Privacy Statement 

  * 1\. Introduction
  * 2\. Collection and Use of Information
  * 3\. Choice
  * 4\. Sharing of Information
  * 5\. Access
  * 6\. Security
  * 7\. Data Integrity
  * 8\. Children
  * 9\. Links to Other Websites
  * 10\. Controlling Unsolicited Email
  * 11\. Amendments
  * 12\. Enforcement, Dispute Resolution, and Verification
  * 13\. Contact Information

**1.    ****Introduction**

JunaidJamshed (Private) Limited (“J.”) values the privacy and security of the information that you share with us. This Privacy Statement applies to information collected through [www.junaidjamshed.net](http://www.junaidjamshed.net/ "www.junaidjamshed.net") (the “[Website](http://www.junaidjamshed.net/)”). This Statement describes how J. collects, uses, shares, protects, or otherwise processes your personal information.

You must read this privacy policy carefully and we recommend that you print and retain a copy for your future reference. By accessing, browsing or otherwise using this Website, you confirm that you have read, understood and agreed to this Privacy Policy in its entirety. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on this Website so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will also email you, should we make any changes, to give you a chance to ask us not to use your information in that way.

**2.    ****Collection and Use of Information**

**2.1.** **Personal Information**

We will only collect information about you if you willingly provide it. The information you provide, which is about you, is referred to as personal information. Please make sure you update your personal information if any of your details change. You may do so by signing into your [account](http://store.junaidjamshed.net/Signup.aspx). 

  * When you register with J. and/or place an order, we need to know your name, delivery address, e-mail address and telephone number. This information allows us to fulfill your order and notify you of the status of your order.
  * When you register with us to receive our monthly newsletter or details of offers or products we will collect your e-mail address. 

**2.2.** **Credit** **Card Details** ** **

We do not collect Credit Card information. Neither do we save nor do we ask you to provide any credit card or any other payment option related critical information.

**2.3.** **Customer Service Correspondence**

J. also collects information involving customer service correspondence. This information may include emails, internet chats, faxes, or telephone calls directed to our customer service centers. J. processes this information to provide customer service, handle complaints or disputes, measure and improve our customer service, detect and prevent fraud, and detect and prevent violations of our legal agreements. J. retains customer service information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

**2.4.** **Cookies, Web Beacons, and Logs**

J. collects information related to your use of our website using cookies, web beacons, and log information.

Cookies are small files containing strings of text stored on your computer. J. uses cookies to authenticate you as a user when you log in, track your session, deliver content specific to your preferences and interests, store the contents of your shopping cart, provide features related to payment and customer service, and provide other functions.

Web beacons are objects embedded into web pages that allow us to determine whether and for how long users view web pages. We use web beacons for site traffic reporting, unique visitor counts, auditing and reporting, personalization, and other functions.

Log information may include web requests, Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser type, browser language, date and time of your request, and cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. J. uses this information to enhance the functionality of itsWebsite and to make your access more convenient, secure, and efficient.

You may stop your browser from accepting cookies or web beacons. The Help portion of your browser should explain how to configure your browser’s cookie handling. Your browser may have add-ons that may help you block web beacons. You may have limited functionality if you block cookies or web beacons set by our Website.

**2.5.** **Google Analytics**

J. uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service. Google Analytics uses cookies, web beacons, and other means to help J. analyze how users use the site. You may find Google’s Privacy Policy at <http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacypolicy.html> 

**3.** **Choice**

We will seek your consent prior to using your personal information in a manner incompatible with the purposes we described in our Privacy Statement at the time of collection. You may choose not to provide any personal information to J., in which case we will be unable to provide services to you.

**4.** **Sharing of Information**

J. only shares information as described in this Privacy Statement.

J. may disclose personal information where:

  * required by law or by an order or requirement of a court, administrative agency, or other government entity, or by court rules concerning the production of records;
  * J. has reasonable grounds to believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, privacy, property, or safety of our users or others;
  * J. has reasonable grounds to believe that the information relates to the breach of an agreement or violation of the law that has been, is being, or is about to be committed;
  * it is necessary for fraud protection, risk reduction, or the establishment or collection of funds owed to us;
  * it is necessary to enforce or apply our legal agreements, to pursue remedies, or to limit damages to J.;
  * the information is public;
  * you have provided consent or with your direction; or
  * other reasons allow it or other laws require it.

When we are required or permitted to disclose information, we will not disclose more information than is necessary to fulfill the disclosure purpose.

J. may disclose aggregate or statistical information to our business partners, for public relations purposes, or other purposes.

**5.** **Access**

You can access and change/correct your personal information under **[my account](http://store.junaidjamshed.net/Signup.aspx)**   **,** after logging into your account. However if an order has been dispatched/initiated we will not be able to change delivery address or other particulars related to that order.

**6.** **Security**

J. combines technical and physical safeguards with employee policies and procedures to protect your information. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information. We will also continue to assess new technology for protecting information and upgrade our information security systems when appropriate.

Further, we permit only authorized J. employees and third parties to access any personal information. If an employee misuses personal information, we may take disciplinary action, up to and including termination of employment. If any third party individual or organization misuses personal information, we will take action, up to and including termination of any agreement between J. and that individual or organization.

**7.** **Data Integrity**

J. processes personal information only for the purposes it was originally collected and in accordance with this Privacy Statement. J. takes commercially reasonable steps to ensure that the personal data is relevant, reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and current for the purposes for which it is used. J. retains information for as long as reasonably required for business purposes or as reasonably required to comply with our legal obligations.

**8.** **Children**

J. does not sell products for purchase by children, but we do sell children's products for purchase by adults. We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personal information from children under age 18. If you are under age 18, do not share personal information with us.

**9.** **Links to Other Websites**

When you click on a link on this website that takes you to a website operated by another company, you will be subject to that company’s privacy practices.

**10.** **Controlling Unsolicited Email**

We may send you information about our products and services. You may log into the account and update your Preferences to stop receiving this information. You may also opt out of J.’s marketing list or update your information by notifying us at privacy@junaidjamshed.net at any time.

**11.** **Amendments**

J. may amend this Privacy Statement on one or more occasions by posting a revised statement on this Website or a similar website that replaces this Website.

**12.** **Enforcement, Dispute Resolution, and Verification**

Please contact us with any questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement by using the address listed in the Contact Information section below. We will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints or disputes regarding personal information in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

**13.** **Contact Information**

If you have questions or concerns related to this Privacy Statement, you may contact us by email at privacy@junaidjamshed.net or by writing to us at:

Attn: Privacy Officer

JunaidJamshed (Private) Limited.

PLOT # 615, 616/1-CC/2 KURTA GALI,

MAIN TARIQ ROAD, P.E.C.H.S., KARACHI.
